<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[YK.]]></title>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-01-21T21:09:27-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://loonyuni.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Youny Kuang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[loonyuni@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolution 3 Day Juice Cleanse]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/21/evolution-3-day-juice-cleanse/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-21T20:20:02-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/21/evolution-3-day-juice-cleanse</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>Pregame</h3>

<p>I gained <strong>20</strong> pounds in college. I don’t think I need to explain the unhealthy eating habits that easily became me. Something that I also noticed within my freshmen and sophomore years is the more and more I studied, the less I went to uhh &ldquo;party&rdquo;, and the less I felt the pressure to “look good”. Not to sound vain, but it’s true, less skimpy clothes and more sweat pants gave me a lot more room to uhh… inflate. I think it’s fine that my priorities had shifted from health to education, but now that that’s over with. I’m shifting back!</p>

<p>I used to be so into health and fitness in high school, there were days when I would run 6 miles and then play 4 hours of tennis. Cross country and Hot Yoga were so extreme that what I put into my body directly affected my performance the next day. I think anyone who has exercised daily, or partook in a sport can relate to that direct correlation of the quality of input to output.</p>

<p>So these past few weeks that I’ve had off from school has been pretty darn great! I got an unlimited <a href="https://www.groupon.com/deals/bikram-yoga-bellevue-5">Hot Yoga Groupon</a>. My mom had 2 weeks of free gym passes, and she’s also a huge health nut. You know, all organic, free range, no added salt, oil, etc. So being around her and eating her food has definitely helped.</p>

<p>With this combination, I’ve already lost at most 7 pounds! I say at most because eating/drinking out with friends causes this to fluctuate. Also due to Hot Yoga, some of this weight loss may just be water weight. But, with every day that I go to the gym, or attend a Hot Yoga session, I find myself being able to run longer, push harder, and get stronger. And I have oh so missed those feelings.</p>

<h2>The Juice Cleanse</h2>

<p>So now, Jan 18 2015, I have decided to do a juice cleanse. It is more of a challenge, than for weight loss. After a bit of research, I chose to do the <a href="http://www.evolutionfresh.com/3DaysToGreen/">Evolution 3 day juice cleanse</a>. They’re having a 20% off deal right now, so it ends up being about $26 a day, which for a person that eats out a lot (like I used to), isn’t too bad! You can sort of choose whatever packs you want for each day, they have an <strong>easy pack</strong>, which is sweeter and I guess better for beginners, a <strong>balanced pack</strong> which is supposed to be a better nutrient supplement, and a <strong>green pack</strong> which is exactly what it sounds like, lots of greens.  You can also get organic packs, and customize your own packs. Each pack comes with 6 juices, and you’re supposed to drink those 6 juices per day of the cleanse. I decided to go with 2 green packs (because I always loved the green machine from Naked, and I thought it would have less sugar), and one balanced pack, just to mix it up, or <em>balance</em> it out.</p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://i.imgur.com/fejZkZj.jpg" width="350"></p>

<h3>Day One - Green Pack</h3>

<p><img class="center" src="http://i.imgur.com/vMKNrsE.jpg" width="350"></p>

<h5>10 AM</h5>

<hr />

<p> I started off with the Essential Greens w/ Lime. Pretty arbitrary choice. They had two non-green juices in this pack, and I thought that a green juice may have more substance. Be warned, this tastes nothing like Naked’s Green Machine. These are cold pressed juices, not smoothies, and there are no fruits in this drink. It’s literally got the viscosity of water. It’s only got 6g of sugar, and I can taste the kale quite well. Overall though, tolerable, and I feel healthy already :).</p>

<h5>12:30 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p><img class="center" src="http://i.imgur.com/uXCXk0p.jpg" width="350"></p>

<p>A friend from SF was visiting and we went out to lunch at Lot 3… I got a half salad, that may have had way too much blue cheese for a cleanse! I also had a couple of fries (And I really only mean a couple). Over this weekend I also met a bunch of Australian friends that work for <a href="https://www.shoesofprey.com/">Shoes of Prey</a>, and they told me to try an Australian snack, and because it’s the last chance I would be able to do so, I tried it. It was a tim tam cookie. lol. I also drank some green tea in between.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h5>4:00 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>Most likely due to my earlier feast, I felt hungry and drank a Sweet Greens and Lemon. Which tastes exactly like Sweet Greens with Lime, but perhaps a bit sweeter. It has an apple in it as well, so that would explain it. Refreshing, but not fulfilling.</p>

<h5>5:25 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>Got hungry again, Coconut Water and Greens. I am a big fan of this juice. Much sweeter, but actually with less sugar! (9g) om nom nom nom.</p>

<h5>6:30 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>Hot Yoga Session, prior to this I drank a big glass of water and brought in the Spicy Lemonade juice in with me. My mom partook in the session too! :) It was her first time. She didn’t really get any of the postures right but she never took any breaks. Definitely proud of her. I also thought it was an amazing session, never had such an easy one before! Not sure if it’s because of the juices, but definitely very energized!</p>

<h5>8:30 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>Drank an Essential Greens with Lime for “dinner”</p>

<h5>11:30 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>Planning Asia trip with Thomas… very very hungry right now. omg.</p>

<h3>Day 2 - Balance Pack</h3>

<h5>9:30 AM</h5>

<hr />

<p>Gotta love not having to wake up early :) I started the day off with Organic V because I was kind of over green stuff. The Organic V has carrots, beets, spinach, celery, apple and ginger. The carrot and celery are very bold flavors, not too bad.</p>

<h5>2:30 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>Got my wisdom teeth taken out. But it was so fast! And I don’t think I have any swelling. Job well done Dr. Anderson. I sort of planned this juice cleanse around this, as I have to mainly consume liquids anyways! But as hunger stroke, I had a pesto kale salad and a Sweet Greens and Lemon Juice. I had to very slowly chew on the left side of my mouth, I basically swallowed half of these leaves and tomatoes whole.</p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://i.imgur.com/DoGxXFB.jpg" width="350"></p>

<p>For those who don’t know pesto can easily be deliciously made by blending some olive oil, parmesan, and basil together!</p>

<h5>4:00 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>Indulging in a Essential Greens with Lime Juice. meh.</p>

<h5>7:30 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>Had a Ruby Roots juice, very sweet! 25g of sugar and very yummy</p>

<h5>8:45 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>Spicy Lemonade! What a kick! Hiiyah!</p>

<h5>11:00 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>I was a lot more tired today… it might be because I got wisdom teeth taken out or my body needed more fuel.. So, I tried a bit of my brothers protein shake and had  a couple slices of smoked salmon. Both of which are probably super bad. Also, to avoid erupting the clot building in my mouth, I am not allowed to do any real exercise… ahhh. So frustrating.</p>

<h3>Day 3 - Green Pack</h3>

<p>My friend who did the cleanse said that 3 days is the perfect amount. The first day you’re excited, the second day is harder and you just want it to be over with, but already Day 3 appears, and you’ve already made it <em>this</em> far, gotta keep going!</p>

<h5>9:30 AM</h5>

<hr />

<p>Started with the Coconut Water with Greens, because I wanted some sugar. Because I can’t actually exercise, I did some 8 minute abs and blogilates. That lady is so darn peppy!</p>

<h5>11:00 AM</h5>

<hr />

<p>I had the Essential Greens with Lime</p>

<h5>1:00 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>I had a pretty bad lunch of a small avocado, smoked salmon, and sprinkles of gouda cheese. Gahh I’m so bad at this. Sorry I didn’t take a picture! But I feel a lot better than yesterday! I supplemented lunch with Sweet Greens with Lemon :)</p>

<h5>4:00 - 7:00 PM</h5>

<hr />

<p>I had 2 Essential Greens with Lime. I am feeling extremely lethargic. No energy at all. :/ Not sure if it’s the juicing, the wisdom teeth meds, or my lack of exercise, but I am just so tired. Blah. But also! Done! :)</p>

<h3>Conclusions</h3>

<p>It was cool to challenge myself, but overall I think just eating healthy and working out (duh), are enough. I’m sure my stomach has shrunk and maybe I’ll have better portion control from here on out… but I am going to Asia soon so probably not. lol. Anyways, this cleanse was a little hard to gage due to the whole wisdom tooth thing, but overall, I guess I feel healthier? But I don&rsquo;t think I&rsquo;ll be repeating this anytime soon.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like I Can]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/16/like-i-can/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-16T13:51:43-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/16/like-i-can</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<iframe width="560" height="315" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/YQanS-al8Ak" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<p>My sister and I wanted to sing together! So we played around with some harmonies. She&rsquo;s far less tone deaf than I lol.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winter Vacation 2014]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/05/winter-vacation-2014/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-05T22:54:44-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/05/winter-vacation-2014</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<iframe width="420" height="315" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/GV1SyXw0UlQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h1>Carribean Cruise + Florida</h1>

<h2>The Cruise</h2>

<p><em><em>My family doesn’t vacation too much these days, however this year, my savvy Momma had found a great deal on a Caribbean cruise, the 7 day cruise from Dec 21-28 itself was only $600!
We sailed on the Norwegian Epic, which came fully equipped with 3 water slides (one of them was the infamous toilet bowl), a fitness center better than the gym at Berkeley, a jogging track, over 9 dining options, an ice bar, several rock climbing walls, a buttload of shows, pools, casinos, and a whole bunch of other things that you would find in a Las Vegas resort. </em></em></p>

<p>Now this was my first cruise, and people tell you about the abundance of food, but no one really prepares you for the onslaught of food. If you had a functional grhelin (hunger) pathway before, you sure don’t have it anymore.  There was free room service. There was 24/7 dining. There were buffets (with very good food). There were gourmet desserts and restaurants, and there was absolutely <strong>no self control.</strong></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The cruise went had 3 stops, 4 if you include Miami: Nassau, Bahamas; Ocho Rios, Jamaica; and Cozumel, Mexico.</p>

<p>This trip was as touristy as possible. There was no real immersion into any local culture or foods. At each stop, there were rows of &lsquo;Tax and Duty Free&rsquo; jewelry shops. There was even a Hooters at our last stop. (I watched <a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1624431/">this documentary</a> and am now jaded :( )</p>

<p>We had the option of booking &lsquo;shore excursions&rsquo; for each destination, and I am SO glad that we decided to book excursions for each, otherwise all we would be doing was meandering through beach after beach or jewelry store after jewelry store.</p>

<p>The following excursions we took were:</p>

<h3>Atlantis, Nassau, Bahamas</h3>

<p>This was basically a giant resort located in the capitol of the Bahamas. They had a decent sized water park, and an amazing beach. The most memorable slide was the leap of faith, where you drop near vertically down a replica of a Mayan Temple.</p>

<h3>Best of Ocho Rios, Jamaica</h3>

<p>In this excursion, we went to a couple locations and with a guided bus tour. We first went to Dunn River Falls and hiked a waterfall. At first it’s quite exciting, but the thrill is over in 5 minutes. It’s slightly dangerous, but as is any hiking adventure. There were maybe 2 points within the hike where the force of the water was strong enough to worry, and there were always alternative routes or hand rails. I did enjoy it though because you were supposed to form a human chain by holding one another&rsquo;s hands to help each other up the waterfall. Go Teamwork!</p>

<p>We visited a beautiful botanical garden than belonged to a hotel that had been constructed a century ago. We also travelled through the forest on a road they called the Gulley, where road merchants tried selling us many phallic wood carvings.</p>

<p>It was interesting to learn that the minimum wage (which many Jamaicans earn) is $45 US dollars a week. They&rsquo;re gas prices are also currently around $7 US dollars a gallon, and that&rsquo;s with the OPEC war.</p>

<h3>Chankanaab Snorkeling, Cozumel, Mexico</h3>

<p>Here, we went snorkeling, which was beautiful, and I wish I could have better captured some of the amazing fish that I saw with my GoPro, but alas it is hard to swim with a steady hand. We were also lucky enough to have 2 very funny tour guides who taught us about Mayan culture, as many parts of Mexico and the island of Cozumel were once inhabited by Mayans. And then of course we had tequila tastings. I never knew tequila could taste so good! (they had almond flavored tequila!) Then we got to see a very cute sea lion show. Definitely recommend this excursion!</p>

<h2>After the Cruise</h2>

<p>We didn&rsquo;t do too much after the cruise, we went to Universal Studios, and found that so exhausting and expensive, that we decided to abandon our original plan to go to pay $100 to go to Disney World the next day and spend 7 hours waiting in line for 15 minutes worth of rides, and instead go to the Kennedy Space Center.
HOLY MOLY  <strong>KENNEDY SPACE CENTER</strong>. That place, made me want to re-do all of college as an electrical or mechanical engineer. I wanted to be a space cadet. I wanted to be a part of SpaceX or Boeing. They did a phenomenal job of organizing the exhibits. The people who designed the flow of the exhibits are geniuses, I can’t wait to come back again. If/When I become a parent, I will definitely be bringing my kids here when they are of age to inspire them to love science. You can’t not leave wanting to be a scientist.</p>

<p>We also did several other things in Florida like go to the Miami Beach, Everglades National Park, and visit Vizcaya Museum and Gardens all of which were also very enjoyable! (except all the mosquito bites).</p>

<h4>Final Thoughts</h4>

<p>I usually would not be such a fan of this sort of tourism, where false mirrors are put up wherever you go to reflect an image that may make tourists feel at ease. Nonetheless, I gotta say, THIS WAS NICE. The tours were enjoyable, and also meant no real pre-planning needed to be done on our part. Furthermore, there were so many times on the ship where we just did nothing, and looked forward to doing nothing, and often found that the time was nothing &lsquo;o clock. Now, we did plenty of things on the ship, went to almost every show that we could (there were a lot of repeats), they even had the Blue Man Group! Other than the natural family drama that arises when my family congregates, this has got to be the most relaxed I have been since I graduated high school, and it was a great way to end 2014 and my undergraduate career. :)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowerment Project]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2014/12/11/empowerment-project/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-11T17:12:41-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2014/12/11/empowerment-project</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So in FemSex we have had many different projects, all very meaningful, the last one that we had to do was empowerment. Some FemSexies did guided meditation, danced, EFT, and <em>more</em> ;). It was anything that empowers you, or deals with empowerment. So I wrote the little speech below, and performed a song. Because I can&rsquo;t sing through written words, I recorded a youtube video of the song I chose to sing for my recital, which, was <em>WAY</em> out of my league. So sorry that it&rsquo;s really pitchy, but NOT sorry for trying :).</p>

<p><strong>Empowerment Project:</strong></p>

<p>I used  be one sassy 5 year old. I don’t know where the validation of this cocky brattiness stemmed from, but I wish I still had some of that. I don’t know if it was elementary school bullying, or what occasion, or even when, but I know by middle school, I had become a very scared to shine, or stand out. I saw how a lot of kids, mainly girls who weren&rsquo;t afraid to show off their skills, got talked a lot about behind their backs. “She’s trying too hard”, “She just wants all the attention”… etc. So I think somewhere along there, I tried not to take the spotlight. That and a series of rejections, from elections, auditions, and heck even boys, made me doubt my self worth. I think we do sort of live in a society where modesty is appreciated, but I realize now that my view of modesty has been skewed.</p>

<blockquote><p>You see, being modest is not about suppressing your own sense of self worth. Rather, being modest is about uplifting the positive virtues of others with respect to your own. So being able to recognize other people’s talents and abilities as well.</p>

<p>Now let&rsquo;s consider confidence. I believe that confidence has less to do with how much self worth you have, and more to do with where you derive your self worth.<sup>1</sup></p></blockquote>

<!--more-->


<p>So, one big example for me, is singing. I love to sing. But I never really sing in front of people. I’ll sing in the shower, and maybe sing around the house, as I’m comfortable with my family, and turn my car ride to work into a mobile belting booth. But I’ve had a hard time singing in front of people.  There’s always been this fear that I’m not really good enough, and this sort of feeling extended beyond just singing. And even if I was good, I didn’t want people to think of me as those middle school girls had thought about others who tried. I just still have a hard time with accepting any sort of limelight. Furthermore, this anxiety builds up, and even if I were to try and sing in front of people, nerves really throw off your pitch, or memory of lyrics, and all sorts of hullabaloo.</p>

<p>College was even harder, because I was always living with other people, and even if I wasn&rsquo;t, the walls in my apartment are so thin, I can hear my upstairs neighbors phone vibrate. Thus it&rsquo;s been hard for me to find an opportunity to really sing. I had slowly been getting better at singing in front of others, but the majority of the time, I just couldn&rsquo;t. This semester though, I am taking a singing class (Music 44) and we’ve had to do a lot of &ldquo;public singing&rdquo;, and we have a recital coming up! So I’ve started singing more in front of people, and not just the under my breath sort of singing and humming, but like big ass diva shit. Which brings me to my next thing, my favorite singers are Beyonce and Whitney Houston, and when I sing the songs of these queens, my 5 year old inner diva comes out again and I feel empowered as fuck! So if it’s okay with you, I’d like to sing you a bit of a song, it’s lyrics may not be so empowering, but its Whitney, and it’s the shit. And I hope that all of you will never shy away from an opportunity to shine, and keep trying to do something you like because if you don’t try then you won’t be able to get better, and I didn’t even know I could “sing” (decently?) until I actually sang in front of others! I really regret not trying harder to be part of some choir or Acapella group on campus. So fuck bitches who want to put you down, who cares if they think you’re “trying too hard”. That’s right, dammit! I am trying hard, and I don’t think you can ever try too hard to get better at something that you like doing. Being modest is good, but being confident is just as important! And you can definitely be both.</p>

<p>I’m still working on being able to sing, and sing in front of others, but practice makes perfect! On that note, let’s all get boozed up and go karaoke sometime!</p>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yzrK2X60_VY?start=3" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<p><sup>1</sup> <a href="http://qr.ae/qHKDm">Lisa Lin</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seattle Tourism]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2014/12/09/seattle-tourism/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-09T22:32:36-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2014/12/09/seattle-tourism</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>2 summers ago one of my BFF&rsquo;s Eileen came and visited me in Seattle! So I put together this excel sheet! I still feel like a tourist in The Sound (the equivalent of calling SF area The Bay), so these are just what I do with visiting friends, so if you ever find yourself lucky enough to be in the amazing PNW, these are my suggestions on things to do!</p>

<p>Also, go in the Summer if you can, it&rsquo;s 9 months of overcast and light precipitation, but 3 months of heaven in the Summer.</p>

<p><img src="http://i.imgur.com/KajmvuP.png" title="Seattle ToDo!" alt="alt text" /></p>

<p>And here&rsquo;s the Google Drive spreadsheet, let me know if you want to edit the file!</p>

<p><a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1-AOEmCHt2pNJKFyN9RPTU8Wywqpim9fbegYXTaEOFU4/edit?usp=sharing">View Drive Spreadsheet</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Things to Do While at UC Berkeley]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2014/12/09/10-things-to-do-while-at-uc-berkeley/"/>
    <updated>2014-12-09T19:07:26-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2014/12/09/10-things-to-do-while-at-uc-berkeley</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Some of the following will be very simple, things that you would hear about within 10 minutes of being in Berkeley. Others are not even specific to Berkeley, but I think are very meaningful, and others are small things that I have discovered while at Berkeley and are responsible for some of my favorite memories here.</p>

<h4>1. Go to the Marina!</h4>

<ul>
<li>Checkout Takara Sake and go <strong>Sake Tasting!</strong></li>
<li>Eat brunch at Betty&rsquo;s Oceanview Cafe or Cafe M</li>
<li>Get your groceries from grocery outlet <em>SUPER CHEAP</em></li>
</ul>


<h4>2.  Pseudo Illegal things:</h4>

<p>Be VERY careful if you attempt some of these&hellip; I&rsquo;ve gotten lucky with a slap on the wrist, but being a short asian girl might have helped.</p>

<ul>
<li>Sneak into Memorial Stadium and pretend you&rsquo;re NFL superstar</li>
<li>Sneak into Greek Theater and pretend you&rsquo;re Beyonce/Whitney Houston</li>
<li>Climb onto the window sills of Doe Library (super dope on 420)</li>
<li>It&rsquo;s probably gone, but there used to be a couch on top of one of the clark kerr buildings, you can star gaze or something!</li>
<li>I still need to be employable so I won&rsquo;t say any more.</li>
</ul>


<!--more-->


<h4>3. Go Outside!</h4>

<p>There aren&rsquo;t really that many great trails to run around Berkeley, but these few do the job.</p>

<ul>
<li>Indian Rock</li>
<li>Big C</li>
<li>Fire Trails</li>
<li>Tilden Park</li>
<li>Grizzly Peak</li>
</ul>


<h4>4. Do Research!</h4>

<p> Doesn&rsquo;t matter what field you&rsquo;re in, I think it really shows you what&rsquo;s really happening at Berkeley. Sure it&rsquo;s this great academic institution, but above all else it&rsquo;s a research institution, with some bad ass people. Furthermore Berkeley is a very theoretical school, and research allows you to apply things you learned in class, and research is the stuff happening at the very forefront of the fields, you&rsquo;ll get to help push boundaries! Not only do you learn about your field (or others - who says you have to do research in your own field!?), you get over any fears of talking to professors and grad students, and make long lasting friendships - and hey recommendation letters never hurt nobody! And it may seem intimidating at first to get a research position, but trust me there is no shortage of opportunities.</p>

<h4>5. Stay Well Rounded</h4>

<ul>
<li>It can be very easy to pigeonhole yourself to stay with one group of friends, and I know that by sophomore year, you probably think you already know what you like and want out of your friends, but be open. You never know how someone can change your life (hopefully for the better) if you let them.</li>
<li>And don&rsquo;t forget to take fun classes, requirements are important, and maybe you love Chemistry SO much that you really want to just take all the relevant Chemistry classes possible, even graduate level courses, and that&rsquo;s great, but try to take your breadth requirements seriously, even if you P/NP them, take the opportunity to learn! And take those classes to meet people outside of your major and learn from them! and omg look at that, below are some dope classes I think ya&rsquo;ll should take, and some I wish I took!</li>
</ul>


<h4>6. Stay Classy!</h4>

<ul>
<li>PH 116

<ul>
<li>an easy and pretty insightful class, we had an undercover cop come in and talk about prostitution, we are quite sheltered on campus, but just next door in Oakland there are so many issues that we all should be educated on.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Wealth and Poverty

<ul>
<li>I shouldn&rsquo;t have to say much about this class, the profesor dated Hilary Clinton and then introduced Hil to Bill, so we have him to thank for you know, alll o&#8217; dat. And of course he&rsquo;s one of the biggest proponents of income equality.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>FEMSEX</strong>:

<ul>
<li>It&rsquo;s a decal but holy shit it has changed my life. I cannot encourage you enough to take the course. I think I&rsquo;ll have to write a whole other essay just to explain the importance of this class.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Bike Decal:

<ul>
<li>Biking is awesome, it&rsquo;s good for the enviroment, your glutes, and gets you from point a to point b. Not to mention, bikers are just fucking awesome. This class teaches you how to fix your bike, pretty much essential if you own a bike.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>CS 61A:

<ul>
<li>I didn&rsquo;t take this class, I took E7 :( but even if you have to take this class P/NP, do it. Programming is SO much easier than you think.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><p>CS 70:</p>

<ul>
<li>So up until this class, I was a full on Biology fanatic. 61A will teach you how to program, but this class will teach you how to <em>think</em> (like a Computer Scientist). You <strong>literally</strong> go to class everyday and solve riddles. And that&rsquo;s when I realized that I wanted to do more CS!</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><p>MCB 62:</p>

<ul>
<li>Drugs and the Brain! I never got to take this class, but the title should speak for itself.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><p>Also I do suggest you take a graduate class if you can! Be it a seminar, or whatever, you get to see what the NEXT level is like. And also most of the time, they curve to an A for a bunch of funding reasons.</p></li>
</ul>


<h4>7. MORE FOOD</h4>

<ul>
<li>Burma Superstar

<ul>
<li>You don&rsquo;t come here for normal food. You come here for salads. You NEED to get the <strong>Tea Leaf Salad</strong> and the <strong>Rainbow Salad</strong>. Thank me later.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Daras or Cha&#8217;am

<ul>
<li>So I&rsquo;m in LOVE with Pad Thai, there was a time when I ate it at least once a week. These places are pretty amazing, Cha&#8217;am recently changed their recipe or something but overall, these two bad boys are right next to each other and both super delicious.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Lucky House Thai

<ul>
<li>Come here on Sundays! You get free Thai Iced Tea, and their pad thai is WHITE! Every bit as delicious, but it&rsquo;s interesting.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Brazil Cafe

<ul>
<li>That Cilantro Sauce!! NOMS. Expensive for Berkeley, but so yummies.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Gregoire&rsquo;s

<ul>
<li>Try their Potato ball things once, some love &lsquo;em some hate &#8216;em but, I love any sort of fried potatoes, so my mouth is drooling just writing about them. Anyways for SURE get their <strong>Fried Buttermilk Chicken Sandwich</strong> I have had my fair share of these &ldquo;chicken sandwiches&rdquo; like at Bakesale Betty&rsquo;s, but this one, is <strong>THE BEST</strong> (Thank you Michelle for introducing me to this magical sandwich)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>TOSS

<ul>
<li>I don&rsquo;t know, I just really like their food! It&rsquo;s mongolion grill esque?</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Taras

<ul>
<li>WAY better than ici&rsquo;s. ici&rsquo;s is overrated, but Tara&rsquo;s is so creamy and it&rsquo;s got all the same (if not more) of those avant garde flavors, plus they give you bigger scoops for a cheaper price. I&rsquo;m not a big fan of cones, but Tara&rsquo;s hand made sesame cones are the perfect combination of decadent and crunchy.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Indian Flavors Express / House of Curries

<ul>
<li>I don&rsquo;t know much about Indian Food, but I also just really like these places!</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<h4>8. Study Abroad</h4>

<p>I didn&rsquo;t get to do this, but it&rsquo;s one of my biggest regrets, do this early! Or in the summer, so you can actually take credits like those pesky pre-res that matter (often easier abroad&hellip; if you&rsquo;re into that). Or save up a bunch of breadth classes and take them all at once while you&rsquo;re abroad!</p>

<h4>9. Do Something You Don&rsquo;t Even Think You&rsquo;d Like</h4>

<p>I wish I had joined a dance group, or acapella, or heck Korean Drumming. I found that I tried too hard to be all academic. But think about it! After you graduate, you don&rsquo;t get these sorts of opportunities. I&rsquo;ve been checking out meetup, a website where like minded people can organize and meet, sort of like clubs but it isn&rsquo;t the same! Don&rsquo;t just try and join professional clubs or honor societies, as great as they are, do what my asian parents would call &ldquo;useless&rdquo; activities and start new hobbies!</p>

<p>But also do things that will allow you to contribute back to the community, while learning real skills, like volunteer clubs, no matter what major you are you can apply your skills to help someone. I only know STEM ones such as Blueprint, BEAM, Engineers Without Borders, Suitcase Clinic&hellip; etc. Don&rsquo;t get regrets like me :(</p>

<h4>10. Rock it out!</h4>

<p>You&rsquo;re here to learn. To grow. To change. You&rsquo;re here to find your bridesmaids, your groomsmen. If you are passionate about something, do it! Or hell, do everything until you find out what your passionate about.
That&rsquo;s what I sort of did, and I&rsquo;m still not done figuring all of that out. But I don&rsquo;t <em>completely</em> regret all the time I spent trying all the other things.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
