<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Taiwan | YK.]]></title>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/categories/taiwan/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-17T11:59:36-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://loonyuni.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Youny Kuang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[loonyuni@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwan Part 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/27/taiwan-part-2/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-27T20:09:17-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/27/taiwan-part-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>Kenting</h3>

<p>So we also made a pit stop in Kenting. According to Trip Advisor folklore, Kenting was supposed to be poppin. But Taiwan is just a little too north of the equator and it has more seasons than Thailand. Thus the Taiwan winter meant lots of big Chinese Tour Buses with lots of Chinese families, no party people, and cold beaches.</p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/1.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p>We actually drove by a bus crash, which looked pretty frightening!</p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/crash.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p>But it was still pretty and my first taste of one of those &ldquo;Taiwan Night Markets&rdquo;. Thus we ended up changing our plans and left a day early to Taipei!</p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/kenting_2.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/kenting_1.jpg" width="600"></p>

<h3>Tam Sui - 淡水</h3>

<p>It&rsquo;s like a day market that lines a port, they literally call it Fisherman&rsquo;s Wharf for the SF inclined. We got sugar cane juice, ice cream burritos, these weird tofu bricks, giant ice cream cones, these really gelationous jelly fish looking things that are basically boiled chinese bbq pork encased by rice flour. You know what, let me just show you pictures.</p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/ds_1.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/ds_2.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/ds_3.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/ds_4.jpg" width="600"></p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/ds_5.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/ds_6.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/ds_7.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/ds_8.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p>Also, here&rsquo;s the infamous turkish ice cream guy. I literally had a BALL just watching him. He is a true performer, and you can tell that he genuinely enjoys his job. Apologies for the vertical iPhone footage. [It&rsquo;s actually currently taking its sweet time uploading; so I will update this post as soon as it completes]</p>

<p>Annnd this is one of many &ldquo;American&rdquo; fashion faux pas that we witnessed. The Taiwanese love their patterns lol.</p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/ffp.jpg" width="600"></p>

<h3>Mango Shaved Ice - 芒果冰</h3>

<p>So apparently the Taiwanese are responsible for the invention Pearl Milk Tea (or as my friends and I like to call it: BubzTea). But on top of this amazingly delicious fattening drink, they are also the creators of the equally unhealthy mango shaved ice.</p>

<p>According to Thomas&#8217; uncle, there was a year where mango yield was just off the charts, so they had so much extra mango and couldn&rsquo;t sell it because market value was so low, that some farmer started selling mango shaved ice and it just took off.</p>

<p>Unfortunately, shaved ice hasn&rsquo;t particularly taken off in America. This is not your typical snow cone shaved ice, its more of a creamy fine grained texture. It might as wellnot be called ice. We went to 3 mango shaved ice places through out the trip, and each place was so different! Some of them have the mango infused with the shaved ice, some of them had a mixture of a brown sugar infused shaved ice that had thicker chunks? In any case, they were all delicious and the mangos were on point. It is interesting to see how different Taiwanese mango was from Thai mango&hellip; I gotta say I like the Taiwanese mango more hehe.</p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/mango_1.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p>Jeremy Lin ate at the place where we got the mango shaved ice pictured below!</p>

<p><img src="/images/danshui_mango/mango_2.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p>I can&rsquo;t seem to find the picture of the last mango shaved ice, but it was at the infamous Monster Ice, and was absolutely delicious. We also ordered a bubble milk tea flavored shaved ice, which was bomb diggity, and offered a nice contrast to the almost overly sweet mango.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taroko Gorge - Taiwan]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/27/taroko-gorge/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-27T20:04:01-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/27/taroko-gorge</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Taroko Gorge is <em>Gorge</em>ous!  The view throughout is relatively the same however (sort of like how the Grand Canyon looks pretty much the same)</p>

<p>But it was still very beautiful with many sights/trails to see.</p>

<p>We went straight from the airport to the Taipei train station down to Xin Cheng where our very expensive Airbnb was located.</p>

<p>Our Airbnb hosts were amazing though. They built their Airbnb by hand themselves, and they took us everywhere. They picked us up from the train station, sent us to food, sent us to rent bikes/scooters, taught us to ride scooters, helped us buy fireworks, and made us a chicken in a tin box over a fire.</p>

<p>We were advised by our Airbnb hosts to rent a scooter and go through the gorge, we originally were going to walk. That would have taken us 3 hours which means we probably would have only been able to see a couple of the trails per day.</p>

<p>With a scooter we were basically able to knock out all of the trails from the Gorge entrance to Tian Xiang. There were a couple of trails that were closed down for construction. Taroko Gorge is known to have a lot of rock falls, you can even see a lot of the past ones that have occurred.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s a pretty straight forward park, so I&rsquo;ll just include a map and some of the pictures from the park. I really enjoyed Swallow Grotto, Tian Xiang, Baiyang Waterfall, and Sha Ka Dang trail.</p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/taroko.gif" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/1.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/2.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/3.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/4.jpg" width="600"></p>

<!-- more -->


<p><img src="/images/taroko/5.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/6.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/7.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/8.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/9.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/10.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/11.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/12.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/13.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/14.jpg" width="600"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
