<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Taiwan | YK.]]></title>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/categories/taiwan/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-10T18:14:25-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://loonyuni.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Youny Kuang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[loonyuni@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taroko Gorge - Taiwan]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/27/taroko-gorge/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-27T20:04:01-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/27/taroko-gorge</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Taroko Gorge is <em>Gorge</em>ous!  The view throughout is relatively the same however (sort of like how the Grand Canyon looks pretty much the same)</p>

<p>But it was still very beautiful with many sights/trails to see.</p>

<p>We went straight from the airport to the Taipei train station down to Xin Cheng where our very expensive Airbnb was located.</p>

<p>Our Airbnb hosts were amazing though. They built their Airbnb by hand themselves, and they took us everywhere. They picked us up from the train station, sent us to food, sent us to rent bikes/scooters, taught us to ride scooters, helped us buy fireworks, and made us a chicken in a tin box over a fire.</p>

<p>We were advised by our Airbnb hosts to rent a scooter and go through the gorge, we originally were going to walk. That would have taken us 3 hours which means we probably would have only been able to see a couple of the trails per day.</p>

<p>With a scooter we were basically able to knock out all of the trails from the Gorge entrance to Tian Xiang. There were a couple of trails that were closed down for construction. Taroko Gorge is known to have a lot of rock falls, you can even see a lot of the past ones that have occurred.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s a pretty straight forward park, so I&rsquo;ll just include a map and some of the pictures from the park. I really enjoyed Swallow Grotto, Tian Xiang, Baiyang Waterfall, and Sha Ka Dang trail.</p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/taroko.gif" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/1.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/2.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/3.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/4.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/5.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/6.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/7.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/8.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/9.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/10.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/11.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/12.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/13.jpg" width="600"></p>

<p><img src="/images/taroko/14.jpg" width="600"></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
