<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Thailand | YK.]]></title>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/categories/thailand/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-02-15T00:19:42+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://loonyuni.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Youny Kuang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[loonyuni@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phuket]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/14/phuket/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-14T23:19:03+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/14/phuket</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So&hellip; we got robbed. Not sure when, where, or how. Thomas&#8217; guess is the hostel where about 20 people shared a room, and it was basically a free for all during the Full Moon Party or when everyone was asleep. My guess is there was someone going through our belongings on the bus from Surat Thani to Phuket.</p>

<p>Baiscally, we both thought we were clever, and surreptitiously stashed about $300 in our socks, glasses case, retainer boxes.. etc. ALL GONE. And, we&rsquo;re carrying giant backpacking backpacks, so our stuff isn&rsquo;t on the surface, this stuff is lodged in the abyss of mushed items in our bag.</p>

<p><strong>Lesson Learned:</strong> Don&rsquo;t bring much cash with you, and just use the ATM, or just make sure you bring it with you at all times (and don&rsquo;t get pickpocketed)</p>

<p>Anyways.</p>

<p>Because of this recent loss of money, we tried to be very cheap in Phuket, and therefore didn&rsquo;t do much.</p>

<p>We stayed in D&rsquo;s Corner and Guestroom which we found on Airbnb, though she was an AMAZING host, I recommend staying IN Patong, as Phuket is very expensive having been overrun with old tourists with money.</p>

<h2>Patong</h2>

<p>Here was where we had intended to go jet skiing, but again, due to money issues, we decided not to.</p>

<p>The beach was really nice though! Warm calm waters, as the beach is more in a bay. The bad thing about this beach however is that it is extremely touristy. It&rsquo;s impossible to just chill on the beach, as every 3-5 minutes someone is coming up to you, trying to sell you parasailing, jet skiing, juice, beer, mats, necklaces, sunglasses&hellip; you get the point.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/NXtwoB6.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/NXtwoB6.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>We then walked around Patong, and eventually found a really cheap fish spa thing. I&rsquo;m sure you have all heard or seen one of these before, they have these little fish, which I&rsquo;m sure they starve (we saw one fish eating another dead fellow fish at one spa) that will come and supposedly suck the dead skin off your feet. It was only 100 Baht for 30 minutes, so we decided to try it. It was <strong>SO TICKLISH</strong>. I don&rsquo;t think I had much dead skin hanging off my feet, so I couldn&rsquo;t tell much of a difference, but my skin did feel raw which I&rsquo;m sure 30 minutes of sucking will do to you.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/lnZ2Kpg.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/lnZ2Kpg.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<!-- more -->


<h3>Boxing</h3>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/XBdW74q.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/XBdW74q.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>Aside from Lumpini Boxing Stadium in Bangkok, we heard the next best thing was the Patong Boxing. So we paid 1,300 Baht each to watch some boxing.</p>

<p>There were a total of 8 matches, the first 4 were between kids. Like 14 year old boys. It was weird to watch.</p>

<p>The 5th match was two girls! Pretty cool. We saw 2 K.O.&rsquo;s and there were a lot of people gambling (a part of me thinks it was rigged but whatever)</p>

<p>It was cool to see, you get to witness a lot of the culture involved. From the tradition of dancing to honor the sport before each match to the synchronized &ldquo;EYY&rdquo;&rsquo;s and &ldquo;OOOH&rdquo;&rsquo;s from the crowd with each successful hit. (And also the music and gambling) But at the end of the day it&rsquo;s really hit or miss on who the fighers are, I guess if you have more knowledge on the local fighters than you would know who to watch, but we just went because it was convenient, and the fights were so-so.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/GaThwlg.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/GaThwlg.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>I think watching boxing on television is fun, but I think seeing it in person, watching one person hurt another live was kind of hard to watch.</p>

<p>Thomas also got a bomb ass haircut for $5. Complete with a nice fade and they even handled his wacky cowlick!</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/has6W0u.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/has6W0u.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<h3>Phuket Day 2</h3>

<p>The next day we basically just wasted until we got on our flight to Bangkok, where we would then take a train to Chiang Mai. Which was FAR more fun.</p>

<p>Although we did enjoy this Thai Iced Tea, and a lot of guava shakes.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/C6OxDGn.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/C6OxDGn.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Koh Phangan]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/05/koh-phangan/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-05T00:41:56+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/05/koh-phangan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We took a bus from Surat Thani to Donsak and then a ferry from Donsak to Koh Phangan. (I also suggest you buy everything as a package deal from Hualamphong Station or other travel agencies). We tried planning ahead for too many things, and it may have bit us in the butt, as we ended up paying for each leg of the trip individually.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/nXv5z0W.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/nXv5z0W.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>We stayed at Bed n&#8217; Bar right next to Haadrin Beach. I definitely recommend you look for a hostel right near the beach if you plan on attending Full Moon Party (FMP). And also suggest you try to book in advance as the rooms fill up quickly. Using Hostel World should be pretty sufficient.</p>

<p>We made quite a few new friends from the hostel, there&rsquo;s Ruben, Tomas, Maya, and Sigort. Ruben is from Portugal, Tomas from the Czech Republic, and Maya and Sigort from Denmark. We mainly hung out on the beaches and walked around the shops near Haadrin Beach until the second night, when FMP occurred.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/EOjP9b3.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/EOjP9b3.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>It&rsquo;s insane. Everyone gets painted in neon paint, and is decked out in flower head wreaths and neon tanks.</p>

<p>Some designs you can get painted on you:</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/LgPCTgR.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/LgPCTgR.jpg</a>&#8221; width=&#8221;700&#8221;></p>

<p>The entire beach was covered with human beings. Everyone wasted drunk from sketchy vodka buckets. By 3 AM everyone seemed to be making out with someone. I have many videos, but you can do a quick google images search to see just how crazy this party is. The party kept going on all the way until 9 AM. There were people from all over the world (mainly europe), and of all ages. We saw an old man pull out coke and another old man yell &ldquo; YOU CHEEKY BASTARD! &rdquo;. There was mushroom mountain, and there were ropes of fire. An epic party to say the least.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/JTFxmS2.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/JTFxmS2.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Oh! Another pro of living right near haadrin beach is that you don&rsquo;t have to pay an entrance fee to the party, nor pay for a taxi or ferry to get to the location.</p>

<p>And it is here, that my fake Birkenstocks were stolen. I also lost a pair of shorts and sunglasses. &hellip;sigh, shit happens.</p>

<p>We left Koh Phangnan at 9 AM, meaning we only really got 3 hours of sleep, and spent the entirety of 2/4/15 on busses and ferrys getting to Phuket. We are finally in Phuket, and dismayed to find that things are super expensive here (relative to Bangkok). :(</p>

<h5>Digressions:</h5>

<p>I&rsquo;ve also had a dandy time trying a bunch of unique Lay&rsquo;s chips flavors here. There&rsquo;s Scallops, Nori, Ribs, and some other flavor that I couldn&rsquo;t figure out.</p>

<p>There are more 7 Eleven&rsquo;s here than there are Starbucks in Manhattan. I had heard before that 7 Eleven in some Asian countries is quite posh, but this is something else. 7 Eleven here is the go to store for almost everything. I love it.</p>

<p>Lastly, if you don&rsquo;t want to pay to eat bugs there&rsquo;s a nice restaurant next to the fried chicken stand near Haadrin Beach that will place parts of dead flies in your Pad Thai for free -_-.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/equgmIC.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/equgmIC.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>But if you want some damn good schnitzel, or fried chicken sandwiches, go to Mama Schnitzel. 5 stars.
<img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/GYoRZ9s.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/GYoRZ9s.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangkok Day 3 &amp; 4]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/05/bangkok-day-3-and-4/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-05T00:41:47+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/05/bangkok-day-3-and-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>An update on our &ldquo;illnesses&rdquo;, we proceeded henceforth to eat plenty of yogurt each day and tried our best to eat more fiber. We believe that the initial cause for intestinal unrest was due to this weird porridge we had decided to try the morning of day 2. We hanve since then been much more consistent in our daily BM&rsquo;s. lol. Bring probiotic pills friends.</p>

<h2>Day 3</h2>

<p>There really isn&rsquo;t that much to do in Bangkok, and with the pollution, it makes it somewhat uncomfortable to breathe. I heard that this is standard across most Asian cities though.</p>

<p>We started Day 3 off by going to JJ Market which is only open on weekends, and it was a blast! It&rsquo;s like MBK on steroids and outdoors. There are alleyways and endless opportunities to buy insanely cheap goods, and also counterfeit designer thingamajigs.</p>

<p>I bought myself a pair of fake white Birkenstocks, which later get stolen at a hostel. They were of terrible quality, and I hope that the loss of these short live $8 Birkenstocks was a blessing in disguise.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/0q46b8B.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/0q46b8B.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>Thomas bought 3 pairs of uniqlo type shorts for 300 baht, a 69 baht belt, and a bunch of socks. We also ate lots of food at the market, and saw some cool street food tricks. Unfortunately, I will not upload these videos right now.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/U2HP5iN.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/U2HP5iN.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>We then went to go watch a movie as we heard that the Thai movie experience is something else. Before each movie there is a tribute to their king, and everyone must stand up during this time in the theater. We went to the theater in Terminal 21, which is a cute airport themed mall, (yay more malls!) The seats were nice, but apparently there are way nicer set ups. We watched American Sniper, which I thought was a very good movie! The ending was a bit sad, but I thought it was quite educational, I read somewhere that this is the most accurate portrayal of army life (for the &lsquo;War on Terrorism&rsquo;) thus far.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/uvFHc4W.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/uvFHc4W.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>We then decided to go to Thip Samai, which I have been told by a coupld of sources is the best Pad Thai in Bangkok. Sure enough, when we go there, there was a line that was comparable to that of Cheeseboard on a Friday night. We got two Super Pad Thai&rsquo;s which were basically pad thai wrapped up in an omelet. It was definitely the best pad thai I have had so far in bangkok. Surprisingly, I still enjoy the pad thai options I had in Berkeley more. oops.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/rxEKCak.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/rxEKCak.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>Because we took public transportation, we were much too tired to do anything else and went home to crash.</p>

<h2>Day 4</h2>

<p>We visited Asiatique, which is yet another market, but it&rsquo;s more of a pier, decked out with a ferris wheel and posh western restaurants and pubs lining the waterfront. We went during the day as we had a night train later that evening. Big mistake. It was a complete ghost town when we went, but based on google images, this place is quite scenic and a great photo op at night.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/GkACriQ.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/GkACriQ.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>We then went back to MBK to chill in air conditioning until around 4 and started walking to Hualamphong Train Station.</p>

<p>There happened to be a blood drive going on outside of MBK and we watched what seemed like a Drill routine but more fluid and probably the most perfect synchronization I have ever seen, followed by a couple of live music performances. They were very very talented singers!</p>

<p>Finally we arrived at the train station, and waited for yet another 2 hours. In that time we decided to start watching John Wick. I don&rsquo;t know why, but it seems that I have become very keen on watching violent movies. This movie was filled with mindless action, but it was amazing.</p>

<p>The train was cool, literally. If you ever book an overnight train, pay an extra 50 to 100 baht to get the lower bunk, or bring a big fleece blanket. The upper bunks were freezing cold. Other than that, it was a smooth ride down to Surat Thani.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/EmmnD0u.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/EmmnD0u.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangkok Day 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/31/bangkok-day-2/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-31T09:04:21+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/31/bangkok-day-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Day Two</h2>

<p>This day is not nearly as exciting. Thomas and I on top of still being jet lagged both came down with uhh.. GI issues. It&rsquo;s amazing how much spontaneous fluids exiting your body can really ruin an outing. We both had some diarrhea issues, and I just got my period. Thomas on the other hand, felt like he was going to vomit. Just, not a good combination.</p>

<h4>TaoLin Chan Floating Market</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/T9VCaSM.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/T9VCaSM.jpg</a>&#8221;>
We bussed all the way here, only to find that it was closed contrary to what all the websites said :(. We almost got scammed from a laady trying to get us to take a boat, but argued and then ran away from the angry thai lady. We met other fellow wanderers who made the same mistake, we ultimately decided to bus back and check out Central World and EatThai at the bottom floor of Central Embassy. Central World was again, super high end stuff, but nice to see. The Eatthai food court was really cool, it had little stations, each representing a region of Thailand. We tried two fried rice dishes from Northern Thailand, a Curry dish from Southern Thailand, and some coconut shaved ice as well as a watermelon slushie.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/R9GqrCT.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/R9GqrCT.jpg</a>&#8221;>
<img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/5wIPQiv.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/5wIPQiv.jpg</a>&#8221;>
<img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/zsZvSXb.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/zsZvSXb.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>Because of our &ldquo;illness&rdquo;, we then went back to our hostel/hotel and accidentally napped for 3 hours. oops.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>Chinatown - Yaorawat Road</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/ZCNXVLq.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/ZCNXVLq.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>We took the 4 bus here, and it was nice! Though there were lots of red and gold signs everywhere, there was not much chinese food, and if there were some it had heavy thai influence. Overall food was still good though and it was fun to see.</p>

<p>They also had so much Durien! Nom nom nom</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/SOGEmEy.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/SOGEmEy.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<h4>Soi Cowboy and Patpong Night Market</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/25cCNx8.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/25cCNx8.jpg</a>&#8221;>
<img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/0E1lfin.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/0E1lfin.jpg</a>&#8221;>
We really wanted to see the ping pong show. We first went to Soi Cowboy and there was only really &lsquo;strip clubs&rsquo; there. I wouldn&rsquo;t say they were really strip clubs because it was just a bunch of girls in bikinis awkwardly dancing near poles. (not on, mind you, just next to) It was also very awkward dancing, some of them could swivel their hips farely well, but a lot of them didn&rsquo;t seem like they wanted to be there, and some were trying to dance but it was just&hellip; very bad.</p>

<p>We then went to Patpong and entered a dingy club called SUPER PUSSY, all the ladies seemed post menopausal, but alas the ping pong show had arrived. A lady shot several ping pong balls at Thomas, and another opened two beer bottles and hit us with the cap. Very impressive. There were also ladies who wrote with their v-jays, and even SMOKED cigs! You know that magic trick where a magician pulls seemingly infinite colored scarves from their mouths, we basically saw that but through their vagines. It wass 300 baht per person, and after every &ldquo;show&rdquo;, they try and get you to pay 100 baht tip. We were not okay with that as the entry fee was so high, but it could easily add up quickly. Our club was also super empty, which made it seem more awkward and perverted than say if there was a crowd. I had read tips online on how to view the show, and they had similar pricings. I have had friends who have gone and seen a lot more, i.e., darts being shot out at balloons, fruits being shot into baskets, live animals crawl out such as small birds and rats!, and razor blades.  Overall I guess it was worth it, and it really is a once in a lifetime thing, as in, I don&rsquo;t think I&rsquo;ll ever do that again.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangkok Day 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/30/bangkok-day-1/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-30T08:31:27+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/30/bangkok-day-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>Preamble</h3>

<p>I&rsquo;d like to say sorry that the only pictures we seem to have are selfies, a lot of the go pro pictures didn&rsquo;t turn out well, BUT we have hella videos, they just take ages to upload, so I&rsquo;ll do that after the trip. And I&rsquo;d also like to apologize for just how word vomitty these posts are. They&rsquo;re very much, we did this, then this, and then that, then some of this and then that. Too tired to write well!</p>

<h2>Day One</h2>

<h4>Grand Palace</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/pyiOHNq.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/pyiOHNq.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>The entry fee was 500 Baht!! It was pretty, but not worth 500. I&rsquo;d say go to Wat Arun and just pay 50 Baht for their fee or go to the the National Museum right next door for also less baht and more knowledge, as it is a museum and not just pretty buildings.
There was a long road littered with stands; herb stands, food stands, keychain stands, etc. This road connected you from the Grand Palace to the neighboring National Museum and one of the best Universities in Thailand, Chulangkorn University. At this point we were extremely jet lagged, and had spent quite some baht cabbing to the Grand Palace. We decided to check in to our AirBnb.</p>

<h4>Lee Travel Inn</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/IspQVaO.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/IspQVaO.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>We totally made a mistake in planning (almost) everything. Prices seem a lot cheaper here than on AirBnb, but I guess planning allows us for peace of mind, and regardless everything is pretty cheap. We like this place! However we chose a room with no A/C, just a fan, which means we&rsquo;ve been sleeping with as little clothing as possible. Luckily there seem to be no mosquitos in this fine establishment, so we&rsquo;re good. It&rsquo;s very clean, and sort of hostel-y, everyone has their own independent rooms, and there are shared bathrooms and showers. We have our own shower/bathroom which is nice. The shower water is not heated, but that&rsquo;s no big deal, and flushing is done manually. Furthermore, <strong><em>*Bring Toilet Paper!!</em></strong> everywhere you go, this place doesn&rsquo;t have any, and so do a lot of public restrooms. Wifi is only available in the lobby, which is sort of nice, you get to meet other people this way.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>Lumphini Park</h4>

<p>At this point to save money and to wander, we decided to walk to Khao San Road. On the way we bumped into Lumphini Park which was crazy fun. It&rsquo;s this huge beautiful park, but the absolute best part were all the &ldquo;Workout Machines&rdquo;. I only took video, and uploading is very hard, but I&rsquo;ll do it ASAP.</p>

<h4>MBK</h4>

<p>Oh man, when at first Thomas said we needed to go look at malls, I thought, &ldquo;woop-dee-doo&rdquo;. Like when I tell people visiting Bellevue/Seattle to visit Bellevue Square, it&rsquo;s really just a mall. But THIS, oh no, THIS was no ordinary mall, it was a 7 story consumers mania. It was basically like indoor, air conditioned, clean stands. The stores were all very small, with very affordable prices. Each floor had a theme, the 5th was like electronics, 7th food, and everything else was basically clothes and purses as far as i was aware. I needed a small purse, so I bought one for 200 Baht! That&rsquo;s about $6, so of course, we bought another purse for Thomas&#8217; Mom. We bought some charging cords, and one fo those things so you can suction your phone onto your car while driving. We decided to try out their food court, and ate some saffron rice and curry chicken. It was only about 45 baht. Not bad! Another thing we noticed, portion sizes are on point here. Sure you&rsquo;re paying only $1.50 for your meal, but it&rsquo;s just the right amount of food!</p>

<p>We then meandered around and went to the visiting Siam Ccenter and Siam Paragon which was like the crystal shops at the Aria. Here you will find your Gucci, your pucci, and other italian designer things.</p>

<p>Another interesting thing, we have met far more Chinese than Americans. Some Australian and UK hailing tourists, but very few english speaking otherwise. So, being bilingual has been such a blessing, as it led us to follow two old asian men, running onto a moving bus, that would lead us to Khao San Road, for 16 baht. That&rsquo;s 8 baht each. And since then, we have been trying to bus as much as possible! So cheap!</p>

<h4>Khao San Road</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/mwR4VI8.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/mwR4VI8.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>&lsquo;FARANG EVERYWHERE&rsquo;. That&rsquo;s what we are, foreigners, or farang. It is a lively touristy road with more popup shops everywhere. Lots of beer and street food. The beer here is good, but its $2, which I think is quite high! But their beer is very good! Light, but at the saem time a decent alcohol percentage. We tried two different pad thai&rsquo;s, and I got to say, I am sad. (Street) Pad Thai in thailand is nothing like Pad Thai in the USA! There&rsquo;s like no tamarind paste, but there is definitely lots of tamarind here, I see other vendors selling that shit like candy.</p>

<p>We then met these two ladies buying some fried bugs to eat, while we were watching them try to haggle and then actually begin to eat their bugs, a chinese man came around, buying a whole BOX of these pupae like bugs, and he said they were his favorite. Because we were asking so many questions, he gave Thomas and I each one to try. (Thank you kind stanger?) They were uhh, definitely very protein rich. I was not a fan, and we quickly went to buy some fried chicken and coconut ice cream to wash out the flavor.</p>

<p>We also decided to get a Massage on the road. SO worth. only 120 baht each for a half hour in heaven. We&rsquo;re already looking very forward to our next full body Thai Massage.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/Ol9zEJF.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/Ol9zEJF.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
