<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Thailand | YK.]]></title>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/categories/thailand/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-03-05T22:32:55-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://loonyuni.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Youny Kuang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[loonyuni@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chiang Mai!]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/14/chiang-mai/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-14T07:19:11-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/14/chiang-mai</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>YAY CHIANG MAI!</h2>

<p>In Chiang Mai we met up with Eileen and Ivan &lt;3 !</p>

<p>{% img /images/tuktuk_together.jpg 550 %}</p>

<p>The first night we went into Old Chiang Mai, and the flower festival happened to be going on! It apparently only occurs like 3 times in February, so we were quite lucky!</p>

<p>{% img /images/flower_fest.JPG %}</p>

<p>We then to visit the Sunday Market which is right behind Tapthae Gate. It was a lively market, with lots of food, similar to the many other night markets we had visited previously. <strong>BUT</strong>, everything was much cheaper. The selection may have been smaller, but if you are looking for any of those famous &ldquo;Thai Tourist&rdquo; pants/shorts or some pashminas, wait until you get to Chiang Mai before purchasing.</p>

<p>We also all got 1 hour Thai Massages for 180 Baht, which is an insane deal. And it felt <em>sooo</em> good. Eileen said these massages were far better than the ones she experienced in Cambodia.</p>

<h2>Skyline Adventures</h2>

<p>The next day we signed up for a Skyline Adventures package where you pay 1,800 baht per person, and they pick you up from the hotel and take you on adventures lol.</p>

<h3>Elephants</h3>

<p>First the bus took us to ride elephants. I know, I know, riding elephants is bad. And we saw them use the bow hook tool to hit the elephants as well as tug on their ear to direct them. Eileen and Ivan also went to an elephant conservatory in Cambodia, and Thomas and I also read online a lot of the horrors that come along with elephant/tiger exhibition. But it was part of the package deal and we decided to just do it :/.</p>

<p>{% img /images/elephantear.jpg 550 %}</p>

<p>Anyways, we got to see one of the elephants poo in the river, and these majestic creatures have equally majestic excrements. They were the size of bowling  balls, and they just kept going! As we were traversing the river, our elephant decided to suck in some mixture of water and sand to spray upon itself to cool itself down. However, we were riding upon said elephant, so Thomas and I got sprayed with these small rocks and water. It was surprising, hilarious, and a little gross. Thomas had this big piece of elephant snot on his cheek lol.</p>

<p>{% img /images/booger.jpg 550 %}</p>

<p>Side note, they were using a car battery to power a printer for pictures! How cool is that</p>

<p>{% img /images/printer_car.JPG 550 %}</p>

<h3>Bamboo Rafting</h3>

<p>This was awesome! It&rsquo;s exactly what it sounds like, but the river they take you around is so peaceful and beautiful. We also had really playful tour guides who managed to get us all soaking wet, and a very funny mishap happened with Thomas where the guide jumped over a tree branch and convinced Thomas to do the same when you were in fact supposed to go under the branch. What ensued was a confused Thomas falling into the river as the bamboo raft glided away.</p>

<p>It was sort of like extreme scenic paddleboarding.</p>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/l6c7m-oJyQM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<h3>Ziplining</h3>

<p>Ziplining in the states is about $120. If we were to say that each of these activities (there being a total of 3) were given the same cost, then that would mean ziplining in Thailand is about $20 per person. That&rsquo;s INSANE.</p>

<p>There were a total of 19 different platforms. Some of them were sort of &ldquo;ropes course&rdquo; like, while the majority were ziplining from platform to platform.</p>

<p>One of the final ziplines was SUPER long, not sure how many meters it was but the view was amazing! We also had the option of doing the zipline &ldquo;Superman Style&rdquo; for this one, where instead of being harnessed in the front at your waist, you were harnessed on your back between your shoulder blades, allowing you to &ldquo;fly&rdquo; like superman! So much fun!!</p>

<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tXuuH8ZORTI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>


<p>We then went to get some more massages, this time I tried an oil massage. It was what you imagine when you think massage, and definitely relaxing. But I definitely prefer the traditional Thai Massage.</p>

<h3>Bar Scene!</h3>

<p>We went to the Bars (just look up <strong>Zoe in Yellow</strong>), and we got it poppin! The DJ&rsquo;s were hella good, and we danced our asses off! The drinks are more expensive, but they&rsquo;re still cheaper than SF drinks ;).</p>

<h3>Nong Buak Park</h3>

<p>In the south west corner of old Chiang Mai, there is this park. Which is very cute! We bought a huge bag of fish/bird feed? for 10 Baht. And we killed 2 hours there luring pigeons in and then scaring them. Thomas even managed to catch a bird with his feet!</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s a nice park, and there were many people having picnics and sunbathing near the pond.</p>

<h3>Thai Cooking Class</h3>

<p>Dude!! These are amazing. Small somewhat of a digression; even as an ethnically Chinese person, when I walk into a 99 Ranch, I have no idea how to use 90% of the things in that store. The 10% I do know is from what little I have picked up from watching my parents. But the same goes for trying to cook Thai food. Without knowledge of what ingredients to buy, and what they look like, or what they&rsquo;re called, you can&rsquo;t really cook authentically!</p>

<p>We learned everything needed to cook most Thai dishes, and even made our own curry paste! It was very fun, and you definitely learn a lot. They also give you a recipe book and a little certificate saying you completed the course lol. I cannot wait to cook Thai food at home! :)</p>

<p>{% img /images/apron.JPG 550%}</p>

<p>{% img /images/fire.JPG 550%}</p>

<p>{% img /images/group_cook.jpg 550%}</p>

<h3>Doi Suthep</h3>

<p>This is a temple at one of the highest points in Chiang Mai, and everyone told us that you have not visited Chiang Mai until you&rsquo;ve visited Doi Suthep. On top of climbing a mountain by taxi to get there, you have to climb 306 steps (which really wasn&rsquo;t that bad at all..) to get to &ldquo;360&rdquo; panoramic views of Chiang Mai.</p>

<p>There was so much construction going on at Doi Suthep, as well as foggy weather, that we were deprived of the promised views. The temple was indeed pretty however, but overall, it was too similar to the many many temples we had already visited before.</p>

<h3>Monk Chats</h3>

<p>A really cool thing that Chiang Mai has is Monk Chats. At almost every temple, there is a time in the day where many young monks will sit at tables and conversate with you about Bhuddism and Monk Life. They spend about 3 hours a week learning English, and this is part of their practice.</p>

<p>We went to Wat ChediLuang and talked to a couple of monks, and during the process we met three &ldquo;missionaries&rdquo;, they&rsquo;re not allowed to say they&rsquo;re missionaries in Thailand or something. But it was really cool learning about what they were doing! They had already spent 3 months in Guatemala, and 2 months in Thailand. They were heading to South Africa next, and were big fans of the cheap tattoos in Thailand haha.
We also talked to one monk who&rsquo;s english was more proficient, and he explained to us the journey of becoming a monk. From 7-20 years old they are novice, and after that they have the option of becoming &ldquo;Monk&rdquo; if they believe they are ready.</p>

<p>They also have extensive schooling where they attend the same schools as the other Thai students, but they have designated &ldquo;Monk&rdquo; tracks. I won&rsquo;t keep going, and let you learn for yourself when you talk to them! :)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phuket]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/14/phuket/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-14T07:19:03-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/14/phuket</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So&hellip; we got robbed. Not sure when, where, or how. Thomas&#8217; guess is the hostel where about 20 people shared a room, and it was basically a free for all during the Full Moon Party or when everyone was asleep. My guess is there was someone going through our belongings on the bus from Surat Thani to Phuket.</p>

<p>Baiscally, we both thought we were clever, and surreptitiously stashed about $300 in our socks, glasses case, retainer boxes.. etc. ALL GONE. And, we&rsquo;re carrying giant backpacking backpacks, so our stuff isn&rsquo;t on the surface, this stuff is lodged in the abyss of mushed items in our bag.</p>

<p><strong>Lesson Learned:</strong> Don&rsquo;t bring much cash with you, and just use the ATM, or just make sure you bring it with you at all times (and don&rsquo;t get pickpocketed)</p>

<p>Anyways.</p>

<p>Because of this recent loss of money, we tried to be very cheap in Phuket, and therefore didn&rsquo;t do much.</p>

<p>We stayed in D&rsquo;s Corner and Guestroom which we found on Airbnb, though she was an AMAZING host, I recommend staying IN Patong, as Phuket is very expensive having been overrun with old tourists with money.</p>

<h2>Patong</h2>

<p>Here was where we had intended to go jet skiing, but again, due to money issues, we decided not to.</p>

<p>The beach was really nice though! Warm calm waters, as the beach is more in a bay. The bad thing about this beach however is that it is extremely touristy. It&rsquo;s impossible to just chill on the beach, as every 3-5 minutes someone is coming up to you, trying to sell you parasailing, jet skiing, juice, beer, mats, necklaces, sunglasses&hellip; you get the point.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/NXtwoB6.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/NXtwoB6.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>We then walked around Patong, and eventually found a really cheap fish spa thing. I&rsquo;m sure you have all heard or seen one of these before, they have these little fish, which I&rsquo;m sure they starve (we saw one fish eating another dead fellow fish at one spa) that will come and supposedly suck the dead skin off your feet. It was only 100 Baht for 30 minutes, so we decided to try it. It was <strong>SO TICKLISH</strong>. I don&rsquo;t think I had much dead skin hanging off my feet, so I couldn&rsquo;t tell much of a difference, but my skin did feel raw which I&rsquo;m sure 30 minutes of sucking will do to you.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/lnZ2Kpg.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/lnZ2Kpg.jpg</a> %}</p>

<!-- more -->


<h3>Boxing</h3>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/XBdW74q.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/XBdW74q.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>Aside from Lumpini Boxing Stadium in Bangkok, we heard the next best thing was the Patong Boxing. So we paid 1,300 Baht each to watch some boxing.</p>

<p>There were a total of 8 matches, the first 4 were between kids. Like 14 year old boys. It was weird to watch.</p>

<p>The 5th match was two girls! Pretty cool. We saw 2 K.O.&rsquo;s and there were a lot of people gambling (a part of me thinks it was rigged but whatever)</p>

<p>It was cool to see, you get to witness a lot of the culture involved. From the tradition of dancing to honor the sport before each match to the synchronized &ldquo;EYY&rdquo;&rsquo;s and &ldquo;OOOH&rdquo;&rsquo;s from the crowd with each successful hit. (And also the music and gambling) But at the end of the day it&rsquo;s really hit or miss on who the fighers are, I guess if you have more knowledge on the local fighters than you would know who to watch, but we just went because it was convenient, and the fights were so-so.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/GaThwlg.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/GaThwlg.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>I think watching boxing on television is fun, but I think seeing it in person, watching one person hurt another live was kind of hard to watch.</p>

<p>Thomas also got a bomb ass haircut for $5. Complete with a nice fade and they even handled his wacky cowlick!</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/has6W0u.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/has6W0u.jpg</a> %}</p>

<h3>Phuket Day 2</h3>

<p>The next day we basically just wasted until we got on our flight to Bangkok, where we would then take a train to Chiang Mai. Which was FAR more fun.</p>

<p>Although we did enjoy this Thai Iced Tea, and a lot of guava shakes.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/C6OxDGn.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/C6OxDGn.jpg</a> %}</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Koh Phangan]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/04/koh-phangan/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-04T08:41:56-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/04/koh-phangan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We took a bus from Surat Thani to Donsak and then a ferry from Donsak to Koh Phangan. (I also suggest you buy everything as a package deal from Hualamphong Station or other travel agencies). We tried planning ahead for too many things, and it may have bit us in the butt, as we ended up paying for each leg of the trip individually.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/nXv5z0W.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/nXv5z0W.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>We stayed at Bed n&#8217; Bar right next to Haadrin Beach. I definitely recommend you look for a hostel right near the beach if you plan on attending Full Moon Party (FMP). And also suggest you try to book in advance as the rooms fill up quickly. Using Hostel World should be pretty sufficient.</p>

<p>We made quite a few new friends from the hostel, there&rsquo;s Ruben, Tomas, Maya, and Sigort. Ruben is from Portugal, Tomas from the Czech Republic, and Maya and Sigort from Denmark. We mainly hung out on the beaches and walked around the shops near Haadrin Beach until the second night, when FMP occurred.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/EOjP9b3.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/EOjP9b3.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s insane. Everyone gets painted in neon paint, and is decked out in flower head wreaths and neon tanks.</p>

<p>Some designs you can get painted on you:</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/LgPCTgR.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/LgPCTgR.jpg</a> 700 %}</p>

<p>The entire beach was covered with human beings. Everyone wasted drunk from sketchy vodka buckets. By 3 AM everyone seemed to be making out with someone. I have many videos, but you can do a quick google images search to see just how crazy this party is. The party kept going on all the way until 9 AM. There were people from all over the world (mainly europe), and of all ages. We saw an old man pull out coke and another old man yell &ldquo; YOU CHEEKY BASTARD! &rdquo;. There was mushroom mountain, and there were ropes of fire. An epic party to say the least.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/JTFxmS2.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/JTFxmS2.jpg</a> %}</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Oh! Another pro of living right near haadrin beach is that you don&rsquo;t have to pay an entrance fee to the party, nor pay for a taxi or ferry to get to the location.</p>

<p>And it is here, that my fake Birkenstocks were stolen. I also lost a pair of shorts and sunglasses. &hellip;sigh, shit happens.</p>

<p>We left Koh Phangnan at 9 AM, meaning we only really got 3 hours of sleep, and spent the entirety of 2/4/15 on busses and ferrys getting to Phuket. We are finally in Phuket, and dismayed to find that things are super expensive here (relative to Bangkok). :(</p>

<h5>Digressions:</h5>

<p>I&rsquo;ve also had a dandy time trying a bunch of unique Lay&rsquo;s chips flavors here. There&rsquo;s Scallops, Nori, Ribs, and some other flavor that I couldn&rsquo;t figure out.</p>

<p>There are more 7 Eleven&rsquo;s here than there are Starbucks in Manhattan. I had heard before that 7 Eleven in some Asian countries is quite posh, but this is something else. 7 Eleven here is the go to store for almost everything. I love it.</p>

<p>Lastly, if you don&rsquo;t want to pay to eat bugs there&rsquo;s a nice restaurant next to the fried chicken stand near Haadrin Beach that will place parts of dead flies in your Pad Thai for free -_-.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/equgmIC.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/equgmIC.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>But if you want some damn good schnitzel, or fried chicken sandwiches, go to Mama Schnitzel. 5 stars.
{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/GYoRZ9s.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/GYoRZ9s.jpg</a> %}</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangkok Day 3 &amp; 4]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/04/bangkok-day-3-and-4/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-04T08:41:47-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/02/04/bangkok-day-3-and-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>An update on our &ldquo;illnesses&rdquo;, we proceeded henceforth to eat plenty of yogurt each day and tried our best to eat more fiber. We believe that the initial cause for intestinal unrest was due to this weird porridge we had decided to try the morning of day 2. We hanve since then been much more consistent in our daily BM&rsquo;s. lol. Bring probiotic pills friends.</p>

<h2>Day 3</h2>

<p>There really isn&rsquo;t that much to do in Bangkok, and with the pollution, it makes it somewhat uncomfortable to breathe. I heard that this is standard across most Asian cities though.</p>

<p>We started Day 3 off by going to JJ Market which is only open on weekends, and it was a blast! It&rsquo;s like MBK on steroids and outdoors. There are alleyways and endless opportunities to buy insanely cheap goods, and also counterfeit designer thingamajigs.</p>

<p>I bought myself a pair of fake white Birkenstocks, which later get stolen at a hostel. They were of terrible quality, and I hope that the loss of these short live $8 Birkenstocks was a blessing in disguise.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/0q46b8B.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/0q46b8B.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>Thomas bought 3 pairs of uniqlo type shorts for 300 baht, a 69 baht belt, and a bunch of socks. We also ate lots of food at the market, and saw some cool street food tricks. Unfortunately, I will not upload these videos right now.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/U2HP5iN.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/U2HP5iN.jpg</a> %}</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>We then went to go watch a movie as we heard that the Thai movie experience is something else. Before each movie there is a tribute to their king, and everyone must stand up during this time in the theater. We went to the theater in Terminal 21, which is a cute airport themed mall, (yay more malls!) The seats were nice, but apparently there are way nicer set ups. We watched American Sniper, which I thought was a very good movie! The ending was a bit sad, but I thought it was quite educational, I read somewhere that this is the most accurate portrayal of army life (for the &lsquo;War on Terrorism&rsquo;) thus far.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/uvFHc4W.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/uvFHc4W.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>We then decided to go to Thip Samai, which I have been told by a coupld of sources is the best Pad Thai in Bangkok. Sure enough, when we go there, there was a line that was comparable to that of Cheeseboard on a Friday night. We got two Super Pad Thai&rsquo;s which were basically pad thai wrapped up in an omelet. It was definitely the best pad thai I have had so far in bangkok. Surprisingly, I still enjoy the pad thai options I had in Berkeley more. oops.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/rxEKCak.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/rxEKCak.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>Because we took public transportation, we were much too tired to do anything else and went home to crash.</p>

<h2>Day 4</h2>

<p>We visited Asiatique, which is yet another market, but it&rsquo;s more of a pier, decked out with a ferris wheel and posh western restaurants and pubs lining the waterfront. We went during the day as we had a night train later that evening. Big mistake. It was a complete ghost town when we went, but based on google images, this place is quite scenic and a great photo op at night.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/GkACriQ.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/GkACriQ.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>We then went back to MBK to chill in air conditioning until around 4 and started walking to Hualamphong Train Station.</p>

<p>There happened to be a blood drive going on outside of MBK and we watched what seemed like a Drill routine but more fluid and probably the most perfect synchronization I have ever seen, followed by a couple of live music performances. They were very very talented singers!</p>

<p>Finally we arrived at the train station, and waited for yet another 2 hours. In that time we decided to start watching John Wick. I don&rsquo;t know why, but it seems that I have become very keen on watching violent movies. This movie was filled with mindless action, but it was amazing.</p>

<p>The train was cool, literally. If you ever book an overnight train, pay an extra 50 to 100 baht to get the lower bunk, or bring a big fleece blanket. The upper bunks were freezing cold. Other than that, it was a smooth ride down to Surat Thani.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/EmmnD0u.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/EmmnD0u.jpg</a> %}</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangkok Day 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/30/bangkok-day-2/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-30T17:04:21-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/30/bangkok-day-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Day Two</h2>

<p>This day is not nearly as exciting. Thomas and I on top of still being jet lagged both came down with uhh.. GI issues. It&rsquo;s amazing how much spontaneous fluids exiting your body can really ruin an outing. We both had some diarrhea issues, and I just got my period. Thomas on the other hand, felt like he was going to vomit. Just, not a good combination.</p>

<h4>TaoLin Chan Floating Market</h4>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/T9VCaSM.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/T9VCaSM.jpg</a> %}
We bussed all the way here, only to find that it was closed contrary to what all the websites said :(. We almost got scammed from a laady trying to get us to take a boat, but argued and then ran away from the angry thai lady. We met other fellow wanderers who made the same mistake, we ultimately decided to bus back and check out Central World and EatThai at the bottom floor of Central Embassy. Central World was again, super high end stuff, but nice to see. The Eatthai food court was really cool, it had little stations, each representing a region of Thailand. We tried two fried rice dishes from Northern Thailand, a Curry dish from Southern Thailand, and some coconut shaved ice as well as a watermelon slushie.</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/R9GqrCT.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/R9GqrCT.jpg</a> %}
{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/5wIPQiv.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/5wIPQiv.jpg</a> %}
{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/zsZvSXb.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/zsZvSXb.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>Because of our &ldquo;illness&rdquo;, we then went back to our hostel/hotel and accidentally napped for 3 hours. oops.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>Chinatown - Yaorawat Road</h4>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/ZCNXVLq.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/ZCNXVLq.jpg</a> %}</p>

<p>We took the 4 bus here, and it was nice! Though there were lots of red and gold signs everywhere, there was not much chinese food, and if there were some it had heavy thai influence. Overall food was still good though and it was fun to see.</p>

<p>They also had so much Durien! Nom nom nom</p>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/SOGEmEy.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/SOGEmEy.jpg</a> %}</p>

<h4>Soi Cowboy and Patpong Night Market</h4>

<p>{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/25cCNx8.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/25cCNx8.jpg</a> %}
{% img <a href="http://i.imgur.com/0E1lfin.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/0E1lfin.jpg</a> %}
We really wanted to see the ping pong show. We first went to Soi Cowboy and there was only really &lsquo;strip clubs&rsquo; there. I wouldn&rsquo;t say they were really strip clubs because it was just a bunch of girls in bikinis awkwardly dancing near poles. (not on, mind you, just next to) It was also very awkward dancing, some of them could swivel their hips farely well, but a lot of them didn&rsquo;t seem like they wanted to be there, and some were trying to dance but it was just&hellip; very bad.</p>

<p>We then went to Patpong and entered a dingy club called SUPER PUSSY, all the ladies seemed post menopausal, but alas the ping pong show had arrived. A lady shot several ping pong balls at Thomas, and another opened two beer bottles and hit us with the cap. Very impressive. There were also ladies who wrote with their v-jays, and even SMOKED cigs! You know that magic trick where a magician pulls seemingly infinite colored scarves from their mouths, we basically saw that but through their vagines. It wass 300 baht per person, and after every &ldquo;show&rdquo;, they try and get you to pay 100 baht tip. We were not okay with that as the entry fee was so high, but it could easily add up quickly. Our club was also super empty, which made it seem more awkward and perverted than say if there was a crowd. I had read tips online on how to view the show, and they had similar pricings. I have had friends who have gone and seen a lot more, i.e., darts being shot out at balloons, fruits being shot into baskets, live animals crawl out such as small birds and rats!, and razor blades.  Overall I guess it was worth it, and it really is a once in a lifetime thing, as in, I don&rsquo;t think I&rsquo;ll ever do that again.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
