<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Thailand | YK.]]></title>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/categories/thailand/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://loonyuni.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-01-31T08:07:02+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://loonyuni.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Youny Kuang]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[loonyuni@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangkok Day 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/31/bangkok-day-2/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-31T08:04:21+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/31/bangkok-day-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Day Two</h2>

<p>This day is not nearly as exciting. Thomas and I on top of still being jet lagged both came down with uhh.. GI issues. It&rsquo;s amazing how much spontaneous fluids exiting your body can really ruin an outing. We both had some diarrhea issues, and I just got my period. Thomas on the other hand, felt like he was going to vomit. Just, not a good combination.</p>

<h4>TaoLin Chan Floating Market</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/T9VCaSM.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/T9VCaSM.jpg</a>&#8221;>
We bussed all the way here, only to find that it was closed contrary to what all the websites said :(. We almost got scammed from a laady trying to get us to take a boat, but argued and then ran away from the angry thai lady. We met other fellow wanderers who made the same mistake, we ultimately decided to bus back and check out Central World and EatThai at the bottom floor of Central Embassy. Central World was again, super high end stuff, but nice to see. The Eatthai food court was really cool, it had little stations, each representing a region of Thailand. We tried two fried rice dishes from Northern Thailand, a Curry dish from Southern Thailand, and some coconut shaved ice as well as a watermelon slushie.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/R9GqrCT.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/R9GqrCT.jpg</a>&#8221;>
<img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/5wIPQiv.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/5wIPQiv.jpg</a>&#8221;>
<img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/zsZvSXb.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/zsZvSXb.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>Because of our &ldquo;illness&rdquo;, we then went back to our hostel/hotel and accidentally napped for 3 hours. oops.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>Chinatown - Yaorawat Road</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/ZCNXVLq.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/ZCNXVLq.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>We took the 4 bus here, and it was nice! Though there were lots of red and gold signs everywhere, there was not much chinese food, and if there were some it had heavy thai influence. Overall food was still good though and it was fun to see.</p>

<p>They also had so much Durien! Nom nom nom</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/SOGEmEy.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/SOGEmEy.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<h4>Soi Cowboy and Patpong Night Market</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/25cCNx8.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/25cCNx8.jpg</a>&#8221;>
<img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/0E1lfin.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/0E1lfin.jpg</a>&#8221;>
We really wanted to see the ping pong show. We first went to Soi Cowboy and there was only really &lsquo;strip clubs&rsquo; there. I wouldn&rsquo;t say they were really strip clubs because it was just a bunch of girls in bikinis awkwardly dancing near poles. (not on, mind you, just next to) It was also very awkward dancing, some of them could swivel their hips farely well, but a lot of them didn&rsquo;t seem like they wanted to be there, and some were trying to dance but it was just&hellip; very bad.</p>

<p>We then went to Patpong and entered a dingy club called SUPER PUSSY, all the ladies seemed post menopausal, but alas the ping pong show had arrived. A lady shot several ping pong balls at Thomas, and another opened two beer bottles and hit us with the cap. Very impressive. There were also ladies who wrote with their v-jays, and even SMOKED cigs! You know that magic trick where a magician pulls seemingly infinite colored scarves from their mouths, we basically saw that but through their vagines. It wass 300 baht per person, and after every &ldquo;show&rdquo;, they try and get you to pay 100 baht tip. We were not okay with that as the entry fee was so high, but it could easily add up quickly. Our club was also super empty, which made it seem more awkward and perverted than say if there was a crowd. I had read tips online on how to view the show, and they had similar pricings. I have had friends who have gone and seen a lot more, i.e., darts being shot out at balloons, fruits being shot into baskets, live animals crawl out such as small birds and rats!, and razor blades.  Overall I guess it was worth it, and it really is a once in a lifetime thing, as in, I don&rsquo;t think I&rsquo;ll ever do that again.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangkok Day 1]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/30/bangkok-part-1/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-30T07:31:27+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/30/bangkok-part-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>Preamble</h3>

<p>I&rsquo;d like to say sorry that the only pictures we seem to have are selfies, a lot of the go pro pictures didn&rsquo;t turn out well, BUT we have hella videos, they just take ages to upload, so I&rsquo;ll do that after the trip. And I&rsquo;d also like to apologize for just how word vomitty these posts are. They&rsquo;re very much, we did this, then this, and then that, then some of this and then that. Too tired to write well!</p>

<h2>Day One</h2>

<h4>Grand Palace</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/pyiOHNq.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/pyiOHNq.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>The entry fee was 500 Baht!! It was pretty, but not worth 500. I&rsquo;d say go to Wat Arun and just pay 50 Baht for their fee or go to the the National Museum right next door for also less baht and more knowledge, as it is a museum and not just pretty buildings.
There was a long road littered with stands; herb stands, food stands, keychain stands, etc. This road connected you from the Grand Palace to the neighboring National Museum and one of the best Universities in Thailand, Chulangkorn University. At this point we were extremely jet lagged, and had spent quite some baht cabbing to the Grand Palace. We decided to check in to our AirBnb.</p>

<h4>Lee Travel Inn</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/IspQVaO.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/IspQVaO.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>We totally made a mistake in planning (almost) everything. Prices seem a lot cheaper here than on AirBnb, but I guess planning allows us for peace of mind, and regardless everything is pretty cheap. We like this place! However we chose a room with no A/C, just a fan, which means we&rsquo;ve been sleeping with as little clothing as possible. Luckily there seem to be no mosquitos in this fine establishment, so we&rsquo;re good. It&rsquo;s very clean, and sort of hostel-y, everyone has their own independent rooms, and there are shared bathrooms and showers. We have our own shower/bathroom which is nice. The shower water is not heated, but that&rsquo;s no big deal, and flushing is done manually. Furthermore, <strong><em>*Bring Toilet Paper!!</em></strong> everywhere you go, this place doesn&rsquo;t have any, and so do a lot of public restrooms. Wifi is only available in the lobby, which is sort of nice, you get to meet other people this way.</p>

<!-- more -->


<h4>Lumphini Park</h4>

<p>At this point to save money and to wander, we decided to walk to Khao San Road. On the way we bumped into Lumphini Park which was crazy fun. It&rsquo;s this huge beautiful park, but the absolute best part were all the &ldquo;Workout Machines&rdquo;. I only took video, and uploading is very hard, but I&rsquo;ll do it ASAP.</p>

<h4>MBK</h4>

<p>Oh man, when at first Thomas said we needed to go look at malls, I thought, &ldquo;woop-dee-doo&rdquo;. Like when I tell people visiting Bellevue/Seattle to visit Bellevue Square, it&rsquo;s really just a mall. But THIS, oh no, THIS was no ordinary mall, it was a 7 story consumers mania. It was basically like indoor, air conditioned, clean stands. The stores were all very small, with very affordable prices. Each floor had a theme, the 5th was like electronics, 7th food, and everything else was basically clothes and purses as far as i was aware. I needed a small purse, so I bought one for 200 Baht! That&rsquo;s about $6, so of course, we bought another purse for Thomas&#8217; Mom. We bought some charging cords, and one fo those things so you can suction your phone onto your car while driving. We decided to try out their food court, and ate some saffron rice and curry chicken. It was only about 45 baht. Not bad! Another thing we noticed, portion sizes are on point here. Sure you&rsquo;re paying only $1.50 for your meal, but it&rsquo;s just the right amount of food!</p>

<p>We then meandered around and went to the visiting Siam Ccenter and Siam Paragon which was like the crystal shops at the Aria. Here you will find your Gucci, your pucci, and other italian designer things.</p>

<p>Another interesting thing, we have met far more Chinese than Americans. Some Australian and UK hailing tourists, but very few english speaking otherwise. So, being bilingual has been such a blessing, as it led us to follow two old asian men, running onto a moving bus, that would lead us to Khao San Road, for 16 baht. That&rsquo;s 8 baht each. And since then, we have been trying to bus as much as possible! So cheap!</p>

<h4>Khao San Road</h4>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/mwR4VI8.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/mwR4VI8.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>

<p>&lsquo;FARANG EVERYWHERE&rsquo;. That&rsquo;s what we are, foreigners, or farang. It is a lively touristy road with more popup shops everywhere. Lots of beer and street food. The beer here is good, but its $2, which I think is quite high! But their beer is very good! Light, but at the saem time a decent alcohol percentage. We tried two different pad thai&rsquo;s, and I got to say, I am sad. (Street) Pad Thai in thailand is nothing like Pad Thai in the USA! There&rsquo;s like no tamarind paste, but there is definitely lots of tamarind here, I see other vendors selling that shit like candy.</p>

<p>We then met these two ladies buying some fried bugs to eat, while we were watching them try to haggle and then actually begin to eat their bugs, a chinese man came around, buying a whole BOX of these pupae like bugs, and he said they were his favorite. Because we were asking so many questions, he gave Thomas and I each one to try. (Thank you kind stanger?) They were uhh, definitely very protein rich. I was not a fan, and we quickly went to buy some fried chicken and coconut ice cream to wash out the flavor.</p>

<p>We also decided to get a Massage on the road. SO worth. only 120 baht each for a half hour in heaven. We&rsquo;re already looking very forward to our next full body Thai Massage.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/Ol9zEJF.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/Ol9zEJF.jpg</a>&#8221;></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting to Bangkok]]></title>
    <link href="http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/29/getting-to-bangkok/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-29T01:19:16+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://loonyuni.com/blog/2015/01/29/getting-to-bangkok</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>On the Plane</h2>

<p>I finished gone girl. Even though I had read through the Wikipedia entries for both the novel and the film, I was entraced. (Like a mosquito flying with UV light in sight) It&rsquo;s been a while since I&rsquo;ve read a book - almost a year actually haha. It&rsquo;s such a great feeling when you&rsquo;re immersed in a good book and half of you wants to read slowly; absorbing the metaphors that test your imagination and witty prose that makes you feel sharp, whilst the other half wishes you could read 600 wpm because the plot is so thick with excitement. I struggled between the two and often found myself impatient, skipping and reading every other paragraph near the end only to feel guilty as well as confused and go back to re-read correctly. After finishing, all I could do was think about wanting to watch the movie.</p>

<p>I started &ldquo;Bossypants&rdquo; by Tina fey and listened to a bit of &ldquo;Yes, Please!&rdquo;&ldquo; from Amy Poehler but after Gone Girl their sarcastic memoirs seemed superficial. I know them to be not, these bombastic besties are buzzfeed/tumblr idols of mine but alas I did the opposite of what they probably would do. Gorge myself on airplane food. No, I was not hungry at all at any point on this journey, however my curiosity is stronger than the seam of my high waisted skinny jeans I decided to dawn on my 22 hour transportation fiasco, I don&rsquo;t know the definition of &#8220;traveling comfortably&rdquo;.</p>

<p>All the flights went smoothly, and I was finally reunited with Thomas in Japan. We meandered like fools, looking at every flavor of kit kat bar, and finding all the similarities between Daiso and the real deal. On our flight from Narita to Bangkok we watched Life is Beautiful, it takes some getting used to at first, but once you&rsquo;re in, you&rsquo;re in. A comical yet very poignant movie that follows a life of a vivacious Italian Jew during the times of World War II.</p>

<h2>In Thailand</h2>

<p>We made it! But we&rsquo;ve already been scammed. Our taxi from the airport, charged us per person&hellip; so our fee on the meter said 75 bhat (this is was also after he drove us to the wrong place and we henceforth decided to just walk instead). He charged us 150 bhat. Sure this translates to about 5 dollars, but I am a very broke person right now. We finally get to our hotel which we&rsquo;re only staying in for one night as we thought it&rsquo;d be easiest to deal with because of our late flight. The hotel had a 4 star rating on Kayak, but idk. We walked in and our room is like a haven for mosquitos. There is this fun little master trap thing that&rsquo;s supposed to zap em, but it&rsquo;s not doing the best job possible.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/3SAWyqI.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/3SAWyqI.jpg</a>&#8221; width=&#8221;700&#8221;></p>

<p>Tomorrow is going to be a touristy day, visiting the Grand Palace and National Museum. I hope it will be filled with lots of walking and pad thai. We have also only learned one phrase in Thai, and that is &ldquo;pom pae thaw li sung&rdquo; (only phonetically spelled) which means &ldquo;I am allergic to peanuts&rdquo;. This is because Thomas is allergic to almost every nut, Thailand should be fun. Oh -  and yes, we bought a <a href="http://theoatmeal.com/comics/selfie_stick">selfie stick</a> -  we&rsquo;re still trying to figure out how to use it.</p>

<p><img class="<a" src="href="http://i.imgur.com/MLa8MYV.jpg">http://i.imgur.com/MLa8MYV.jpg</a>&#8221; width=&#8221;700&#8221;></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
